<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Celebration</string>
    <string name="company_descriptipm">Welcome to our event management app designed specifically by 4th semester B.Tech students. With this app, you can easily plan, organize, and manage events for your college, club, family or organization.

Our app provides you with a user-friendly interface that allows you to create and  book events. Whether you\'re planning a small gathering or a large-scale event, our app can help you streamline the process and ensure everything runs smoothly. Or If you are a service provider this app allows you to register the service on the go and get booked quickly. So, download our event management app today and take your event planning to the next level!</string>

    <string name="ashish_msg">"Welcome to Celebration, the ultimate event management app that simplifies the planning and coordination of any celebration. As a full-stack developer, I have leveraged my skills to create a seamless and intuitive platform that streamlines the event planning process. \nWith Celebration, you can easily create and manage your events. The app also have features to register your service for the service providers.\nOur app's user-friendly interface makes it easy for anyone to plan an event, from a small gathering to a large-scale celebration. With Celebration, you can focus on enjoying the event while the app takes care of the details.\nJoin the thousands of users who have already planned their events with Celebration. Download the app today and experience the convenience and ease of event planning at your fingertips.\n \nWarm Regards\nAshish Patel\nFull Stack App Developer"</string>
    <string name="anjali_msg">"Welcome to Celebration, the ultimate event management app and website! Whether you're planning a wedding, birthday party, corporate event, or any other special occasion, Celebration has got you covered. With our intuitive and user-friendly interface, you can easily manage all aspects of your event, from invitations and guest lists to vendor management and budget tracking.At Celebration, we believe that every event should be a memorable and stress-free experience. That's why we've designed our app and the website to be easy to use and packed with features that will make your event planning journey a breeze. So why wait? Sign up for Celebration today and start planning your next event with confidence!\n \nWarm Regards\nAnjali Upadhyay\nWebsite Developer"</string>
    <string name="sarika_msg">"Welcome to Celebration, the all-in-one event planning solution designed to make your life easier. With Celebration, you can plan, organize, and execute events of any size and complexity with confidence and ease.
Whether you're planning a small social gathering or a large-scale conference, Celebration has everything you need to plan a successful event. Our app is designed to streamline the event planning process, giving you more time to focus on what really matters - creating a memorable event for your guests. So why wait? Sign up for Celebration today and start planning your next event like a pro!\n \nWarm Regards\nSarika Kumari\nWebsite Developer"</string>

</resources>